mansurfer.com 2019-08-17

# Privacy Policy

#### I. Introduction

Your privacy is important to Mount Equinox, Inc (ManSurfer.com Parent Company). This privacy policy discloses the information practices for Mansurfer.com, including the types of information we gather and track, how we use that information, and with whom we share it. The purpose of this policy is to let you know how we use your personal information before we collect it. We have tried to include a link to this policy on every page on which personal information is collected.

This is an adult website that expressly and strictly limits its users to adults. All persons under the age of 18 are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents of this website. 

CAREFULLY READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT BECAUSE BY YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THIS WEBSITE YOU WILL BE EXPRESSLY SIGNIFYING THAT YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY STATEMENT AND THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS POLICY STATEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT YOU SHOULD NOT USE THIS SITE. 

#### II. Information Collection and Management

##### A. Personal Information

###### i. Information we collect

“Personally identifiable information” is information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name and e-mail address. Mount Equinox, Inc. only has access to the personally identifiable information that you provide to us. For example, we cannot determine your e-mail address unless you provide it. We cannot gain access to other information on your computer.

Those who visit only public areas of the Website and who do not join as members generally do not, provide us with any personally identifiable information.

Those who wish to join the site or sign up for our mailing list, must provide us with enough personal information to enable us to process the requested transaction. This generally includes, at a minimum, personally identifiable information such as name, e-mail address, date of birth, gender and your photograph, if you choose add one to your profile page. Members also select, and thereby provide, a username and password combination.

###### ii. How we use the information

Your personally identifiable information is used only to process the requested transaction, and occasionally to provide you with special offers from ManSurfer. On occasion, for example, we may send emails to introduce a product or service that we think will interest our subscribers.

ManSurfer will never intentionally disclose any personally identifying information to any third party, unless we are compelled to do so by law (for example, in response to a subpoena or court order), or if our obligation to maintain the privacy of your information has been waived or otherwise excused by you (for example, by your filing suit against us and asserting claims against which such information would be relevant in our defense). Please note that our lawyers, accountants, and/or vendors are not “third parties” for the purpose of this section to the extent that disclosure to them is necessary or desirable for the operation of our business. We may reveal your personal data to any other organization that buys, or to which we transfer all, or substantially all, of our assets and business. If this sale or transfer takes place, we will use reasonable efforts to try to make sure that the organization we transfer your personal data to uses it in line with our privacy policy. 

###### iii. Opt-out policy

Non members don't provide us with any personally identifiable information so there is nothing to opt-out of. For those who choose to join your personal information is required for us to provide services to you as a registered user, you cannot opt-out of providing it and still receive those services. You can opt-out of receiving promotional emails by contacting [support@mansurfer.com](mailto:support@mansurfer.com), or by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter. 

##### B. Click-stream data

###### i. Information we collect

We also collect non-personally identifying information provided by your browser and/or our servers, such as the name and IP address of the domain from which you came from (if any), your IP address - a numerical code to identify your device and which can provide information about the country, region or city where you are based, details of your devices, for example, the unique device ID, unique advertising ID and browsers used to access our content, the amount of time you spent on each page and on the site as a whole, your browsing history of the content you have visited on our sites, and the path you followed through the site. This sort of information is sometimes known as click-stream data.

###### ii. How we use the information

We use click-stream data in the aggregate to analyze trends and statistics and to help us understand how users use our site. This allows us to identify areas and technologies that need improvement, and to provide appropriate bandwidth and technical support for areas that are growing. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level. From time to time we may share this aggregate statistical information with partners, suppliers and other third parties, but it will not include any personally identifiable information.

###### iii. Opt-out policy

Click-stream data is generated by your browser and our servers, and therefore you cannot opt-out of providing it. However, some of the privacy resources listed below may provide a partial solution by (for example) allowing you to cloak your IP address.

##### C. Cookies

###### i. Information we collect

We collect certain non-personally identifying information through the use of “cookies.” A cookie is a small file that a Web site can send to your browser to be stored on your system. Some cookies are deleted when you end your online session (“session cookies”), while others may be stored on your computer indefinitely (“persistent cookies”). We use cookies on this site to store information such as user login status (so that you aren’t forced to enter your username and password on every page). You can view our [Cookie Policy Here](https://www.mansurfer.com/cookies.html).

###### ii. How we use the information

We use the information stored in cookies to personalize your website experience and to manage your online session. The information in cookies is both set and read by our server. We do not share data that we collect from cookies with third parties.

###### iii. Opt-out policy

You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, many areas of the site will not function properly.

##### D. Financial Information

###### i. Information we collect

We do not collect any credit card or financial information. The use of our Web site is free.

###### ii .How we use the information

Since we do not collect your financial information, we do not have it to use.

#### III. Related Issues

###### A. Information security

We are constantly striving to improve the security of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures, such as using encryption, to help us keep your information secure. We will continue to implement additional security measures as new technologies emerge.

###### B. Online advertising

ManSurfer does not use third-party services to provide banner advertising.

###### C. Children’s data

The ManSurfer website is not directed towards children and does not collect any data governed by the United States’ Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). In accordance with 47 U.S.C. § 230(d), we notify you that parental control protections (including computer hardware, software, or filtering services) are commercially available that may assist in limiting access to material that is harmful to minors. You may find information about providers of these protections on the Internet by searching "parental control protection" or similar terms. If minors have access to your computer, please restrain their access to sexually explicit material by using any of the following products, which we provide for informational purposes only and do not endorse: CYBERsitter™ | Net Nanny® | CyberPatrol | ASACP. 

###### D. Privacy technology

There are an increasing number of products and services available to help protect your privacy while navigating the Web. See <http://www.privacyalliance.org/resources/rulesntools/> for an overview of some of these tools. Please note that Mount Equinox, Inc. has not formally evaluated these tools and makes no representations or warranties about them.

###### E. Business relationships

This site contains links to other websites and uses resources by third parties (for example Google Analytics, Disqus, Twitter & CloudFlare). We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the website--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. You can find Disqus's Privacy-policy here **<https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy> and CloudFlare's Privacy-policy here <https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy>. You can find Twitter's Privacy-policy here <https://twitter.com/privacy>.**

Mount Equinox, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. The privacy of information that you provide to those companies is governed by their respective privacy policies and not by that of Mount Equinox, Inc.

**F. Posting comments on our sites**

When you post information on a discussion board or comment publicly on an article on one of our sites, the information you post and your username are publicly accessible. This information can be viewed online and collected by other people. We are not responsible for the way these other people use this information. When contributing to a discussion, we strongly recommend you avoid sharing any personal details, and especially information that can be used to identify you directly such as your name, age, address and name of employer. We are not responsible for the privacy of any identifiable information that you post in our online community or other public pages of the site. 

**G. Data Retention**

We will maintain your information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information. 

**H. Do Not Track**

Please note that we do not alter our website’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

**I. General Data Protection Regulation (Gdpr) Compliance**

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you join our website), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

**J. Behavioral Advertising**

We do not currently use any targeted advertising.

**K. Data security**

We make every effort to protect the transmission and storage of all user information, and to ensure security of our site and systems. But we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-parties illegally obtaining this information. We take all reasonable measures to prevent security breaches. You assume the risk of such security breaches should they occur despite our reasonable security measures.

**L. Notification of changes**

This privacy statement was last updated on May 25th, 2018. Mount Equinox, Inc reserves the right to revise or modify this policy at any time and in any way. This privacy statement may be modified by us by posting changes on this website. Changes to this privacy statement will be considered effective once the changes have been posted to this website. You are responsible for checking this website for any posted changes to this privacy statement. 

#### M. Notice of Rights

Subjects in the European Union are advised of the following rights; Mount Equinox, Inc gladly provides the same opportunities to subjects outside the European Union. (You may have other rights.)

  * You may request access to and rectification or erasure of personal data concerning you. 

  * You may request restriction of data processing concerning you. 

  * You may request the personal data which you have provided concerning you, and you may transmit those data to another party without hindrance from us. 

  * You may object at any time to our processing of personal data concerning you and you may withdraw your consent for future processing. 

  * If you are a subject in the European Union, and you believe that Mount Equinox, Inc’s processing of personal data relating to you infringes the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation, you may lodge a complaint with your Member State’s designated supervisory authority. 

###### N. Questions regarding this statement

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to ManSurfer Privacy coordinator at [support@mansurfer.com](mailto:support@mansurfer.com).

**Contact us**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by emailing [support@mansurfer.com](mailto:support@mansurfer.com).
